ANDREW E DROLLINGER

14730 Sugarpine St | Oregon City, OR 97045 | 503-679-4294 | aedrollinger@live.com | www.linkedin.com/in/dsquared77/

OBJECTIVE

Searching for a long-term, dependable career where my skill set can be used to its greatest potential. I bring to the table excellent communication skills and a great work ethic. My education and administrative work experience would serve as substantial tools to enhance both my future and my organization's success.

EDUCATION

ITT Technical Institute *Graduation Date November 24, 2006*Associates of Computer Science- Computer Network Systems *Spokane, WA*

CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager Administrator Certification 2007- April 2010
- Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager Administrator Certification 2012-June 2013
- MCITP-SharePoint Design and Administration 2010- February 2012
- Avaya Basic and Advanced Phone Systems Administration Certifications- July 2009
- Washington State Security Clearance ID# WA25740316- April 2009
- CompTia Security+ Certification- In progress
- PMI PMP Ceritication Will complete once "Advance" 'ecurity+ is completed
- CompTia Cloud Essentials Certification- Will complete once Network+ is completed

SKILLS PROFILE

Software Skills:

- Windows 7 Enterprise, XP Professional, Apple Operating Systems
- Microsoft Office Suite 03'-13', Project 03'-13', Visio 03'-13', Publisher 07'13'
- Microsoft SharePoint 07'-13', SharePoint Services 3.0, Microsoft InfoPath 07'-13'
- Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager 2007/2012, Windows PowerShell
- Microsoft Data Protection Management, Symantec Altiris Data Recovery Solutions,
 Symantec Software Deployment Console
- Microsoft Windows Server 2003/2008R2, Microsoft SQL Server 2005/2008
- TCP/IP standards, LAN/WAN standards, AppleTalk Network, Watchguard Firewalls
- SysAid help desk ticketing/network monitoring, Spiceworks network monitoring tools
- Adobe Creative Suite Master Collection 5.5 (Acrobat, Lightroom 4, Photoshop, InDesign, etc.)
- Java, Flash, HTML 5, CSS₃, Ruby on Rails, Drupal 7.x-8.x, WordPress, Facebook For Developers
- Google Analytics, Piwik Web Analytics and SEO tools, SAP 7.10/7.20/7.30, Easy DMS 7.1

Hardware Skills:

- Knowledgeable of wireless and hard wired computer network systems
- Knowledgeable of computer, server, and network hardware components
- Avaya digital and IP phone systems

Administrative Skills:

- Very organized with excellent multi-tasking and work prioritization skills with little or no supervision
- Possess a high level of accuracy with strict attention to detail
- Ability to think objectively and can deal with conflicts with diplomatic professionalism
- Exceptional oral and written communication skills
- Exceptionally flexible and motivated personality allows new skills to be learned with ease
- Can relate to others with the greatest of ease, allowing for the ability to work effectively in a team setting
- Perform administrative tasks and maintain employee and customer relations
- Maintain and organize inventory to ensure accountability

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sulzer Pumps Inc IT Specialist Portland, OR

9/17/2010 — Current

- Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager 2012 administration. Windows 7 Deployment utilizing SCCM and MDT
- SharePoint Services 3.0 administration
- Windows Server 2003/2008R2 active directory maintenance
- End user support of 1400+ users and 25 remote sites throughout North America
- Computer Hardware, Software, Network, and VPN support
- Technical writing for documentation
- Create PO's, buyer for companywide hardware and software
- Responsible for receiving and deployment of companywide computers, network hardware and software
- Maintain all computer hardware and software inventory spreadsheets for accurate documentation
- All other duties assigned

City of Pasco Network/PC Specialist

4/20/2009 — 9/1/2010

- Pasco, WA
 - End user support of 500+ users and 25 servers at 10 remote city sites. Support Police Dept., Fire Depts., Public Works, Engineering, Finance, Municipal Court, etc.
 - Windows Server 2003/2008R2 active directory administration. Patch management
 - Implemented, deployed, and administered Microsoft Systems Center Configuration Manager 2007. Windows 7 deployment utilizing SCCM and MDT
 - Configured and administered Sophos Enterprise anti-virus solutions
 - Setup and deployed application servers running Windows Server 2008R2 with IIS
 - Implemented SQL 2008 for data configuration and storage, enterprise software operations, and reporting services
 - Converted the city's analog/digital phone system to an Avaya IP phone system from the ground up
 - Computer Hardware, Software, Network, Server, Analog/Digital and IP phone system support
 - Assigned and administered network location/folder user permissions for all city departments and employees
 - Maintained computer hardware/software licensing and static IP address documentation for accurate records and state audits
- Assembled hardware and software license reports for yearly budgeting
- Administered the help desk system configuration and daily operations
- All other duties assigned

Oregon Coast Aquarium Desktop Administrator Newport, OR

8/1/2008 — 4/10/2009

- SharePoint 2007 implementation and design, deployment, and administration
- End user support of 120+ users and 14 servers
- Windows Server 2003 active directory administration. Patch management
- Computer Hardware, Software, Network, Server, Phone System, Audio and Visual equipment support
- Performed server maintenance, updates and deployment
- Configured weekly incremental and full data backups utilizing Microsoft Data **Protection Management**
- Performed website maintenance and updates
- Maintained and improved social media presence
- All other duties assigned

Westside Motorsports Inventory Manager /Shipping and Receiving /End User Support

10/1/2005

Spokane, WA

12/29/2006

- Maintained an extensive inventory of high value and of volume
- Created PO's, buyer for company merchandise and accessories, tested new product for potential distribution
- Built and maintained positive rapport with all major vendors and manufacturers
- Ship customer orders, return factory parts to vendors, and receive parts and accessories for stock
- Performed network, computer hardware and software support, website filtering and monitoring to maintain business productivity
- All other duties assigned